<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Frome</title>
    <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Frome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.chrisfrome.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Oven Cast Iron Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/dutchovencooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/dutchovencooking/</guid>
      <description>Dutch Oven Cast Iron Cooking One of my favorite things to use for cooking is the dutch oven. I got my first introduction to using cast iron from being in the Boy Scouts. The dutch oven makes for easy one dish meals with easy cleanup. You can make everything from breakfast casseroles to soup/stew, pizza or even dessert. Cast iron in general, is great not just for camping but is great when cooking at home too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laravel</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/Laravel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/Laravel/</guid>
      <description>Laravel with Homestead : Web app Development and Management PHP Docs
Laravel Docs
What is Homestead  Homestead is a pre-packaged vagrant box that provides you will all the development tools that you need by default
 Once you have setup your virtual machine and vagrant, you simply add homestead box to it and all of the development tools are installed automatically for you. This saves you the time of individually installing the required software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Personal Projects  Hugo Website Code This is the github repository that host the hugo code that my wesite is built from
 chrisfrome.com This is the html code for the site that is generated by hugo
 BinConvert This is a Java number Converter. It lets you convert a decimal number to various other number formats
 CS 480 Portfolio Code This is the code used for my final class assignment for CS 480 at JMU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me My name is Chris. I&amp;rsquo;m a recent alumnus of James Madison University (May 2018) where I majored in Computer Science and minored in Environmental Information Systems. My interests within Computer Science include: software engineering/DevOps, full stack web development, and security. I first learned about programming starting in high school, and am excited to start a new career as a Software Engineer. Aside from programming and computer science I enjoy cooking, rock climbing, and camping/the outdoors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>