<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chris Frome</title>
    <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Frome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coin Collecting</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/coincollecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/coincollecting/</guid>
      <description>My Coin Collection Getting Started My coin collecting began when my dad gave me my first coin book. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember my exact age, but I must have been 7 or 8. He have me one of the unfinished Lincoln penny books he had from his collection. I was also given a big book of the U.S. to use for collecting the state quarters (1999 - 2008). From there I have continued to grow my collection and a love for coin collecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch Collecting</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/patchcollecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/patchcollecting/</guid>
      <description> My Patch Collection Getting Started Boy Scouts Council Shoulder Strips Order of the Arrow Pocket Flaps Souvenier Patches Future </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Oven Cast Iron Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/dutchovencooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/dutchovencooking/</guid>
      <description>Dutch Oven Cast Iron Cooking One of my favorite things to use for cooking is the dutch oven. I got my first introduction to using cast iron from being in the Boy Scouts. The dutch oven makes for easy one dish meals with easy cleanup. You can make everything from breakfast casseroles to soup/stew, pizza or even dessert. Cast iron in general, is great not just for camping but is great when cooking at home too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laravel</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/Laravel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chrisfrome.com/post/Laravel/</guid>
      <description>Laravel with Homestead : Web app Development and Management PHP Docs
Laravel Docs
What is Homestead  Homestead is a pre-packaged vagrant box that provides you will all the development tools that you need by default
 Once you have setup your virtual machine and vagrant, you simply add homestead box to it and all of the development tools are installed automatically for you. This saves you the time of individually installing the required software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>